import RecruitmentData from '@data/interface/recruitmentData';

const recruitmentData: RecruitmentData = {
  departmentFaq: [
    {
      departmentName: 'General',
      questions: [
        {
          question: 'When are the days we need to come in?',
          answer:
            'The respective directors will let you know about these details, once you have been shortlisted as a member. The weekly meetings/training sessions will be either after school hours or on the weekends.',
        },
        {
          question:
            'What’s your estimated intake for both operations and technology wing?',
          answer:
            'There is no hard cap. We are happy to take in as many individuals as possible as long as you can commit fully to this cca.',
        },
        {
          question:
            'Considering the current situation, will the CCA meetings/training be held online or offline? Is there a regular meeting session?',
          answer:
            'If the situation becomes better in semester 2, then we will have offline meet-ups and physical events. The regular meeting session depends on which department you are a part or and the type of project you have been assigned to. If you are in Machine Learning or Blockchain, you will have weekly meetings/training sessions. As mentioned in the call, the Machine Learning Department will be conducting those on Saturdays. While working on a project, the workload and frequency of meet-ups will increase to even twice or thrice the norm. As for Software Development, meetings can be weekly or biweekly meetings depending on the project and its deadlines. For Operations, the meetings will be ad hoc. However, we do have a tight schedule, so do expect the meetings and workload to be equivalent to that of taking an additional module!',
        },
        {
          question: 'Will the interview be more technical or more general?',
          answer:
            'The interviews would be mostly general, where the directors try to understand more about you, your capability and your interests. However, if you are interested in becoming a tech lead or in taking up a more technical role under Blockchain, the interview will include more technical questions.',
        },
        {
          question:
            'Does fintech society support entrepreneurship in the fintech space?',
          answer:
            'We are certainly welcome to any idea! FinTech Society has got the resources and partners to support entrepreneurship. Do join us and we can discuss further (:',
        },
        {
          question: 'Difference between FinTech and NUS DSC?',
          answer:
            'Fintech is all about applying technology to improve financial services. We get the opportunity to do research and work on projects with well known companies and organise large scale events in the Finance-Technology domain. FinTech Society prepares you for the industry by giving you opportunities to work with and learn from experts. DSC in short, is all about using tech for social good. So if you are interested in doing volunteer work with the aid of technology, then DSC is the place for you',
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      departmentName: 'Blockchain',
      questions: [
        {
          question:
            "I'm interested in cryptocurrencies but not so interested in the mechanism of blockchain technology. Is the fintech society the right place for me?",
          answer:
            'Yes, you are welcome to join. The biggest application of blockchain is cryptocurrencies. So definitely, this would be covered but it would not be the main focus of this department. For example, under the research division, the Blockchain Department has analysed Binance reports amongst others. Furthermore, you will get to meet more like-minded people within the society who might be interested in cryptocurrencies like yourself (:',
        },
        {
          question:
            'ML and Blockchain is a combined department? Do we have to choose one or both if we join?',
          answer:
            'Our 5 Departments would be Machine Learning, Blockchain, Software Development, Internal Affairs and External Relations. ML and BC are not a combined department. We encourage you to choose one department to commit to for the year. You can definitely just hop into the other departments’ training sessions/workshops.',
        },
        {
          question: 'Is the workload of the training equivalent to CS1010?',
          answer:
            'Workload for training and project will be more or less equivalent to an average 4 MC module (CS1010S being more than average)',
        },
        {
          question: 'Do we need to learn CS2040 or CS1010S?',
          answer: 'It is not a requirement',
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      departmentName: 'Machine Learning',
      questions: [
        {
          question:
            'ML and Blockchain is a combined department? Do we have to choose one or both if we join?',
          answer:
            'Our 5 Departments would be Machine Learning, Blockchain, Software Development, Internal Affairs and External Relations. ML and BC are not a combined department. We encourage you to choose one department to commit to for the year. You can definitely just hop into the other departments’ training sessions/workshops.',
        },
        {
          question: 'Is the workload of the training equivalent to CS1010?',
          answer:
            'Workload for training and project will be more or less equivalent to an average 4 MC module (CS1010S being more than average)',
        },
        {
          question: 'Do we need to learn CS2040 or CS1010S?',
          answer: 'It is not a requirement',
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      departmentName: 'Software Development',
      questions: [
        {
          question: 'What roles are there? Frontend? Backend?',
          answer:
            'We have both frontend and backend projects. There are opportunities to do both types of projects.',
        },
        {
          question: 'Do we need to learn CS2040 or CS1010S?',
          answer: 'It is not a requirement',
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      departmentName: 'Quant',
      questions: [
      ],
    },
    {
      departmentName: 'Operations',
      questions: [
        {
          question:
            'What is the job scope like for external affairs? Can we join without initial blockchain knowledge or experience but instead is interested in internal or external affairs? If I have no prior leadership experiences will the Ops department still take me in?',
          answer:
            'No prior knowledge about this domain is required to be a part of the Operations Wing (Internal Affairs + External Relations). Anyone interested in delving into the FinTech space or simply finding out more about the field can join us! Although prior leadership experience will be a plus, we are open to recruiting members who are responsible, committed and willing to help us with the Operational tasks.',
        },
        {
          question:
            'I am very interested in the operations department but I also hope to learn and gain experience from other departments, for instance machine learning and blockchain. Is that possible?',
          answer:
            'Yes that is possible! You will get to attend webinars and technical workshops to gain some experience. Moreover, you can sit in some of the training sessions as per your interest level. Our goal is for you to get integrated into this space while working with us under the Operations Wing.',
        },
      ],
    },
  ],
};

export default recruitmentData;
